{
    "subject": "resource/Nusrat_Fateh_Ali_Khan",
    "predicate": "property/id",
    "object": "inWKTCcsczQ",
    "human_readable": "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's ID is inWKTCcsczQ.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9065819382667542,
            "question": "What is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's ID?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7281045317649841,
            "question": "Is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615015268325806,
            "question": "Where was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.642099142074585,
            "question": "What is the significance of inWKTCcsczQ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6171530485153198,
            "question": "When was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5728875398635864,
            "question": "Who were some of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's musical collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5126512050628662,
            "question": "What is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's most famous song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49438732862472534,
            "question": "How did Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan influence music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49421489238739014,
            "question": "What genre of music is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4646565318107605,
            "question": "Has Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's ID is inWKTCcsczQ.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1974_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1974_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan influence music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1974_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's most famous song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1974_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1974_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text documents do not mention an ID for Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan as \"inWKTCcsczQ\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the triple \"Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's ID is inWKTCcsczQ\" is supported.\n\nHere is the evaluation:\n\n* The documents mention various facts about Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan, such as his birth and death dates, his profession as a singer of Qawwali, and his international recognition.\n* However, there is no mention of an ID \"inWKTCcsczQ\" associated with him in any of the documents.\n* Therefore, I must conclude that the triple \"Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's ID is inWKTCcsczQ\" is not supported by the provided context information.\n\nThe final answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not contain any information about Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's ID or identifier being \"inWKTCcsczQ.\" Therefore, the triple is incorrect according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}